<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD100">
<display-name>Kabhi Khushi Kabhi Gham (2001) (Family; Romance; Musical)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD100">
<title>(12+) 210min. IMDB rate:7,4.</title>
<desc>Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham...(translation. ) (Sometimes there is joy, sometimes there is sorrow...), also known as simply K3G, is a 2001 Indian Hindi-language drama film written and directed by Karan Johar and produced by Yash Johar. The film stars Amitabh Bachchan, Jaya Bachchan, Shah Rukh Khan, Kajol, Hrithik Roshan and Kareena Kapoor, with special appearance by Rani Mukerji. The score was composed by Babloo Chakravarty. The film's songs were composed by Jatin–Lalit, Sandesh Shandilya and Aadesh Shrivastava, with lyrics by Sameer and Anil Pandey. The film tells the story of an Indian family, which faces troubles and misunderstandings over their adopted son's marriage to a girl belonging to a lower social-economic group than them.
Category: Family, Romance, Musical. 
Director: Karan Johar. 
Year: 2001. 
Country: India.</desc>
<category>Family, Romance, Musical</category>
<icon src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/4/4d/Kabhi_Khushi_Kabhie_Gham..._poster.jpg"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD101">
<display-name>Home Alone (1990) (Family; Children; Comedy)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD101">
<title>(PG) 103min. IMDB rate:7,6.</title>
<desc>Home Alone is a 1990 American comedy blockbuster film directed by Chris Columbus written and produced by John Hughes and distributed by 20th Century Studios. It was followed by two theatrical sequels and two made-for-television films.
Kevin, an eight-year-old boy whose wish of his family to disappear comes true when they mistakenly left him at home when they go on a vacation to Paris for Christmas.
While initially relishing time by himself, he is later greeted by two burglars, Harry and Marv, who are played by Joe Pesci and Daniel Stern, respectively. Kevin eventually manages to outwit them with a series of booby traps.
Category: Family, Children, Comedy. 
Director: Chris Columbus. 
Year: 1990. 
Country: United States.</desc>
<category>Family, Children, Comedy</category>
<icon src="https://encrypted-tbn1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQIgzfRNCJH4LHXl82vI1d7dBCxhlFw4bXWEWiNLtUZzl3YqmHd"/>
</programme> 

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD102">
<display-name>Home Alone - Lost In New York (1992) (Family; Children; Crime)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD102">
<title>(PG) 103min. IMDB rate:6,8.</title>
<desc>Once again it’s Christmas time, and Kevin McCallister (Macaulay Culkin) is back. His Family are planning another Vacation but this time his family is in Miami and he’s in New York City with enough money and credit cards to turn the Big Apple into his own playground. But Kevin won't be alone for long. Two of his oldest enemies are back the notorious Wet Bandits, Harry (Joe Pesci) and Marv (Daniel Stern), still smarting from their last encounter with Kevin, are bound for New York City too, plotting a huge holiday heist. Kevin's ready to welcome them with more battery of booby traps the bumbling bandits will never forget.
Category: Family, Children, Crime. 
Director: Chris Columbus. 
Year: 1992. 
Country: United States.</desc>
<category>Family, Children, Crime</category>
<icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDI1MzM0Y2YtYmIyMS00ODE3LTlhZjEtZTUyNmEzMTNhZWU5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTQxNzMzNDI@._V1_FMjpg_UX1000_.jpg"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD103">
<display-name>Bhoothnath (2008) (Comedy; Drama; Family)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD103">
<title>(PG) 150min. IMDB rate:6,3.</title>
<desc>Aditya is an Engineer on a cruise line, and lives a wealthy lifestyle along with his wife, Anjali, and a school-going son, Aman. They decide to re-locate to Goa and rent a bungalow, 'Nath Villa', that was built in 1964. They are made aware that the bungalow is haunted, but they disregard this. While Aditya returns to work, Aman is enrolled in St. Francis High School, and Anjali hires a drunken thief, Anthony, as a helper to clean the house. Shortly thereafter Aman starts getting in trouble in school, and is reprimanded by Principal J.J. Irani. To make matters worse, he also starts making up stories of a new friend 'Bhoothnath'. Anjali disregards this, but during a stage performance, a local resident tells her that Aman is mimicking the former owner of Nath Villa. Anjali will soon find out that indeed the bungalow is haunted by it's former owner - Kailash Nath - who has taken a morbid liking to Aman, and will not permit them to vacate the house under any circumstance.
Category: Comedy, Drama, Family. 
Director: Vivek Sharma. 
Year: 2008. 
Country: India.</desc>
<category>Comedy, Drama, Family</category>
<icon src="https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSLnqkC4TVjxzGnkJ0Gi3mDf7wN659pw6otJOTR2i8VJAUJDYBZ"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD104">
<display-name>Elf (2003) (Comedy; Family; Adventure)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD104">
<title>(PG) 97min. IMDB rate:6,8.</title>
<desc>On Christmas Eve, a baby at an orphanage crawls into Santa Claus's sack and is unwittingly taken back to the North Pole. Discovering the child at the workshop, the elves name him Buddy after his diaper's brand label and Papa Elf adopts him. Buddy is accepted by the elf community and grows up, thinking he is an elf. But being human sized, Buddy cannot keep up with the workload and is demoted to toy testing. Soon, Buddy overhears that he is a human and Papa Elf explains that Buddy was born to Walter Hobbs and Susan Wells who put him up for adoption before she died. Walter now works as a children's book publisher at the Empire State Building in New York City and is unaware of Buddy's existence. To Buddy's horror, Santa reveals that Walter is on the Naughty List due to his selfishness, but suggests Buddy could help redeem Walter.
Category: Comedy, Family, Adventure. 
Director: Jon Favreau. 
Year: 2003. 
Country: United States.</desc>
<category>Comedy, Family, Adventure</category>
<icon src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzUxNzkzMzQtYjIxZC00NzU0LThkYTQtZjNhNTljMTA1MDA1L2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_.jpg"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD105">
<display-name>Seeta Aur Geeta (1972) (Comedy; Romance; Adventure)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD105">
<title>(12+) 148min. IMDB rate:6,3.</title>
<desc>Seeta lives with her grandma and her cruel aunt Kaushalya, uncle Badrinath, Kaushalya's brother, Ranjeet, and daughter Sheela. Although Seeta is wealthy and owns the property, she is treated worse than a servant by Kaushalya, and Sheela. Ranjeet lusts after her, and uncle Badrinath is a silent spectator. The only emotional support for Seeta is her grandma, who is handicapped and wheelchair bound. One day Seeta, after being beaten by Kaushalya and Ranjeet, for purportedly stealing Ranjeet's wallet, leaves the house, and runs into a man called Raka who calls her "Geeta". She is also introduced to a woman, who calls her daughter. Perplexed at this situation, but having no choice, she stays on. Meanwhile, her look-alike, Geeta, is apprehended by the police and brought back to uncle and aunt. Geeta, unlike Seeta, is unafraid and soon assumes control of the house, and reduces her aunt, cousin, and Ranjeet to mere underlings and servants at her command. She also falls in love with wealthy Dr. Ravi. But as fate could have it, Geeta's cover is blown and she is arrested for impersonation. Seeta, in the meantime, is unable to meet life's harsh demands, including dancing in the street, as was Geeta's and Raka's profession. As Geeta is got rid off, the aunt and Ranjeet locate Seeta and bring her back to her life of mute slavery, abuse, and confinement.
Category: Comedy, Romance, Adventure. 
Director: Ramesh Sippy. 
Year: 1972. 
Country: India.</desc>
<category>Comedy, Romance, Adventure</category>
<icon src="https://encrypted-tbn1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSqu-NHZDWxBEghRW9bbBiGSOkBtXtHtuV8FLoUtcz9qffDnMwR"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD106">
<display-name>DharamVeer (1977) (Action; Romance; Adventure)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD106">
<title>(9+) 165min. IMDB rate:6,7.</title>
<desc>The story revolves around two small kingdoms in British India. Court intrigue, murder, assassination, Royal excesses, injustice to the subjects were hallmarks of the time and find their way into the story. Princess Minakshi of one of the kingdoms hunts tigers and falls in love with warrior hunter Jwala Singh who saves her life. Jwala Singh disappears when out hunting tiger and the stage is set for the drama. The king is not aware that Minakshi married her lover, so Minakshi finds herself the Queen of a neighbouring kingdom while pregnant by Jwala Singh. Court intrigue separates one of the twin boys that she delivers. Grown up, the boys become close friends - the prince (Veer) and the ironsmith (Dharam}. One falls in love with a princess while the other with a seafaring gypsy. How Dharam wins the heart of a haughty princess and how Veer succumbs to the charm and determination of a gypsy girl is a good part of the story. The mastermind of the palace intrigue, Sujan Singh brings together a group of like minded people to help him stage a coup. Dharam Veer was the highest grossing film at the box office, back in the day.
Category: Action, Romance, Adventure. 
Director: Manmohan Desai. 
Year: 1977. 
Country: India.</desc>
<category>Action, Romance, Adventure</category>
<icon src="https://encrypted-tbn3.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcRDDe0l2UNJZZp5yZt39MZ92qmMmgtRqbfY5jeSwNEwhVpJKrdO"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD107">
<display-name>Baabul (2006) (Family; Romance; Drama)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD107">
<title>(PG) 172min. IMDB rate:5,4.</title>
<desc>While golfing, Malvika Talwar meets with handsome, U.S.-returned Avinash, both fall in love with each other, and shortly thereafter get married. The following year, Malvika gives birth to a boy, and they decide to name him Ansh. Then chaos and devastation enters Malvika's life when Avinash gets killed in an automobile accident. Malvika resigns herself to a life of a widow, her sole motive for living appears to be to look after Ansh. She is shocked when her in-laws, Balraj, and Shobhana, ask her to re-marry. Will Malvika be able to remove Avinash from her heart and mind and marry someone else?
Category: Family, Romance, Drama. 
Director: Ravi Chopra. 
Year: 2006. 
Country: India.</desc>
<category>Family, Romance, Drama</category>
<icon src="https://encrypted-tbn1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQgWHiIWEkvQwi-941AcRI0L2JTEPFVi6l81WutOuCiJ5q9bPtT"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD108">
<display-name>Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge (1995) (Musical; Romance; Drama)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD108">
<title>(11+) 189min. IMDB rate:8,1.</title>
<desc>Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge is based on the characters Raj and Simran, played by Shah Rukh Khan and Kajol, are young Indians living in the United Kingdom. Raj is the only son of a rich Indian played by Anupam Kher and Simran is the elder daughter of Amrish Puri. Simran meets Raj on a trip to European countries which she got permission to go after a lot of pleads to her strict dad.After some initial misadventures, they fall in love. Simran goes home and tells her family about her romance. Her father, will have nothing to do with a love marriage, and is adamant that she marry his best friend's son Kuljeet, who is a man full of himself and thinks he is a shikari (Hunter), to whom she has been promised since she was born. Her mother wants to spare Simran, but cannot sway the domineering father.
Category: Musical, Romance, Drama. 
Director: Aditya Chopra & Karan Johar. 
Year: 1995. 
Country: India.</desc>
<category>Musical, Romance, Drama</category>
<icon src="https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcTx2D8JgbglbDHmtcGVWQvOvdyMzGtx77Hvsk3S0fBy-Zop7vyL"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD109">
<display-name>Sholay (1975) (Romance; Action; Adventure)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD109">
<title>(PG) 192min. IMDB rate:9,2.</title>
<desc>Sholay is a 1975 Hindi action-adventure film written by Salim–Javed, directed by Ramesh Sippy, and produced by his father G. P. Sippy. The film is about two criminals, Veeru (Dharmendra) and Jai (Amitabh Bachchan), who are hired by a retired police officer to capture the ruthless dacoit Gabbar Singh. Veeru and Jai's love interests are two innocent girls who are known as Basanti who is a talkative ambitious girl (Hema Malini) and Radha who is a quite down to earth girl who has dreams for happiness (Jaya Badhuri). Sholay is considered a classic with over 90% ratings and is also rated 9.2/10 on Rotten Tomatoes and it is one of the best recommended Indian films.
Category: Romance, Action, Adventure. 
Director: Ramesh Sippy. 
Year: 1975. 
Country: India.</desc>
<category>Romance, Action, Adventure</category>
<icon src="https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSBkfOBfNVBOCkdOLfuw2TG1zWq8-iBtdMVS5Tc2u0xd7Ltj7SIqjYYIfP2&s=10"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD110">
<display-name>Devdas (2002) (Romance; Drama; Musical)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD110">
<title>(12+) 181min. IMDB rate:8,9.</title>
<desc>Devdas is a popular 2002 Indian Hindi-language epic romantic drama film based on a Bengali romantic novel written by Sarat Chandra Chatterjee this movie is directed by Sanjay Leela Bhansali and produced by Bharat Shah under his banner, Mega Bollywood. This movie stars Shah Rukh Khan (Who played Devdas Mukherjee), Aishwarya Rai Bachchan (Who played Paro), and Madhuri Dixit (Who Played Chandramukhi), with Kirron Khmer (Who Played Sumitra), Smita Jaykar (Who Played Kaushalya), and Vijayendra Ghatge (Who Played Bhuvan) in supporting roles. This movie has over 8.5/10 ratings on Rotten Tomatoes.
Category: Romance, Drama, Musical. 
Director: Sanjay Leela Bhansali. 
Year: 2002. 
Country: India.</desc>
<category>Romance, Drama, Musical</category>
<icon src="https://musicart.xboxlive.com/7/c92b1100-0000-0000-0000-000000000002/504/image.jpg?w=1920&h=1080"/>
</programme>

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tv generator-info-name="WebGrab+Plus/w MDB REX Postprocess -- version V2.1.11.0 -- Jan van Straaten" generator-info-url="http://www.webgrabplus.com">
<channel id="VOD111">
<display-name>Baazigar (1993) (Thriller; Drama; Romance)</display-name>
<programme start="20200101000000" stop="99991231235900" channel="VOD111">
<title>(12+) 181min. IMDB rate:7,9.</title>
<desc>Baazigar is a 1993 Indian Hindi-language action romantic thriller suspense crime thriller film directed by Abbas-Mastan and produced by Venus Movies. It’s a film about Ajay Sharma (Shah Rukh Khan) seeking to avenge the fall of his family. It’s starring Kajol playing Priya in the female lead role. On the other hand, Raakhee (Who is playing Shobha), Shilpa Shetty (Who is playing Seema), Dalip Tahil (Who is playing Madan Chopra), Siddharth Ray (Who is playing Karan), and Johnny Lever (Who is playing Babulal) appear in supporting roles, with the film's soundtrack composed by Anu Malik. It is a contemporary thriller about a young man seeking to avenge the fall of his family.
Category: Thriller, Drama, Romance. 
Director: Sanjay Leela Bhansali. 
Year: 1993. 
Country: India.</desc>
<category>Thriller, Drama, Romance</category>
<icon src="https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcRlZIBu-dR8Ufid1CGJy2YNNnmJ_5WU2P2Ohg&usqp=CAU"/>
</programme>
